- Well, I actually might be able to help.
- How so?
(Sheldon:)Like Jane Goodall observing the apes...
(Sheldon:)...I initially saw their interactions
as confusing and unstructured.
(Sheldon:)But patterns emerge.
(Sheldon:)They have their own language,
if you will.
(Leonard:)Go on.
(Sheldon:)Well, it seems that the newcomer
approaches the existing group...
(Sheldon:)...with the greeting,
"How wasted am I?"
(Sheldon:)Which is met
with an approving chorus of "Dude."
(Leonard:)Then what happens?
(Sheldon:)That's as far as I've gotten.
(Leonard:)This is ridiculous.
(Leonard:)- I'm jumping in.
- Good luck.
(Leonard:)No, you're coming with me.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I hardly think so.
(Leonard:)Come on.
- Aren't you afraid I'll embarrass you?
- Yes, but I need a wingman.
All right, but if we're going
to use flight metaphors...
(Sheldon:)...I'm much more suited to being the guy
from the FAA analyzing wreckage.
(Girl in Hippie Costume:)Oh, hi.